[{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pu","A":"Promethium","B":"Plutonium","C":"Praseodymium","D":"Platinum","E":"Polonium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ni","A":"Nitrogen","B":"Neptunium","C":"Nickel","D":"Niobium","E":"Nobelium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ca","A":"Cobalt","B":"Calcium","C":"Carbon","D":"Californium","E":"Cadmium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Mg","A":"Mendelevium","B":"Manganese","C":"Magnesium","D":"Molybdenum","E":"Germanium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ga","A":"Magnesium","B":"Gadolinium","C":"Manganese","D":"Germanium","E":"Gallium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Uuo","A":"Zirconium","B":"Sodium","C":"Ununoctium","D":"Phosphorus","E":"Potassium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cn","A":"Copernicium","B":"Californium","C":"Chlorine","D":"Silicon","E":"Carbon","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Si","A":"Strontium","B":"Sodium","C":"Silicon","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Samarium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Re","A":"Rutherfordium","B":"Roentgenium","C":"Rhenium","D":"Fermium","E":"Ruthenium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Kr","A":"Krypton","B":"Berkelium","C":"Zirconium","D":"Mercury","E":"Europium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Tb","A":"Titanium","B":"Terbium","C":"Bismuth","D":"Tellurium","E":"Cobalt","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ba","A":"Bohrium","B":"Berkelium","C":"Boron","D":"Cobalt","E":"Barium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Tm","A":"Tantalum","B":"Terbium","C":"Titanium","D":"Thallium","E":"Thulium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"He","A":"Hydrogen","B":"Helium","C":"Rutherfordium","D":"Technetium","E":"Ruthenium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"F","A":"Fermium","B":"Francium","C":"Fluorine","D":"Californium","E":"Flerovium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ag","A":"Silver","B":"Gallium","C":"Manganese","D":"Aluminum","E":"Argon","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Lr","A":"Tellurium","B":"Flerovium","C":"Livermorium","D":"Beryllium","E":"Lawrencium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cl","A":"Californium","B":"Chlorine","C":"Calcium","D":"Cobalt","E":"Silicon","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Uus","A":"Ununseptium","B":"Ununtrium","C":"Strontium","D":"Tungsten","E":"Darmstadtium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Bi","A":"Berkelium","B":"Barium","C":"Bromine","D":"Bismuth","E":"Bohrium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Uut","A":"Einsteinium","B":"Ununtrium","C":"Ununseptium","D":"Ununpentium","E":"Ununoctium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cs","A":"Cesium","B":"Copernicium","C":"Chromium","D":"Scandium","E":"Chlorine","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ds","A":"Scandium","B":"Dysprosium","C":"Praseodymium","D":"Sodium","E":"Darmstadtium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ac","A":"Calcium","B":"Actinium","C":"Arsenic","D":"Astatine","E":"Americium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Bh","A":"Bromine","B":"Bohrium","C":"Beryllium","D":"Bismuth","E":"Boron","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pm","A":"Praseodymium","B":"Promethium","C":"Polonium","D":"Potassium","E":"Palladium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sn","A":"Strontium","B":"Selenium","C":"Tin","D":"Scandium","E":"Silicon","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sr","A":"Strontium","B":"Silver","C":"Sulfur","D":"Samarium","E":"Seaborgium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"S","A":"Silicon","B":"Selenium","C":"Sulfur","D":"Strontium","E":"Samarium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rb","A":"Roentgenium","B":"Erbium","C":"Rubidium","D":"Rhenium","E":"Beryllium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Zn","A":"Zinc","B":"Chlorine","C":"Ununseptium","D":"Iodine","E":"Zirconium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"O","A":"Fluorine","B":"Oxygen","C":"Osmium","D":"Ununoctium","E":"Roentgenium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Fe","A":"Flerovium","B":"Francium","C":"Iron","D":"Fluorine","E":"Fermium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Lu","A":"Lutetium","B":"Lanthanum","C":"Lawrencium","D":"Lithium","E":"Livermorium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Br","A":"Barium","B":"Boron","C":"Beryllium","D":"Bromine","E":"Bohrium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sb","A":"Antimony","B":"Sodium","C":"Sulfur","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Silicon","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cr","A":"Chromium","B":"Curium","C":"Cerium","D":"Carbon","E":"Chlorine","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sm","A":"Selenium","B":"Strontium","C":"Seaborgium","D":"Samarium","E":"Sodium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Th","A":"Technetium","B":"Thallium","C":"Tellurium","D":"Thorium","E":"Thulium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ti","A":"Terbium","B":"Thulium","C":"Tellurium","D":"Thallium","E":"Titanium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Po","A":"Promethium","B":"Potassium","C":"Phosphorus","D":"Protactinium","E":"Polonium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pr","A":"Phosphorus","B":"Promethium","C":"Praseodymium","D":"Protactinium","E":"Palladium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Au","A":"Actinium","B":"Americium","C":"Cadmium","D":"Aluminum","E":"Gold","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"W","A":"Gallium","B":"Praseodymium","C":"Technetium","D":"Lawrencium","E":"Tungsten","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"B","A":"Bohrium","B":"Beryllium","C":"Bromine","D":"Boron","E":"Berkelium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Hg","A":"Hydrogen","B":"Mercury","C":"Holmium","D":"Helium","E":"Hassium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cf","A":"Californium","B":"Cobalt","C":"Francium","D":"Calcium","E":"Copernicium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rg","A":"Nitrogen","B":"Argon","C":"Roentgenium","D":"Radon","E":"Rhenium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Tc","A":"Thorium","B":"Tin","C":"Titanium","D":"Technetium","E":"Protactinium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"U","A":"Ununseptium","B":"Uranium","C":"Ununtrium","D":"Ununpentium","E":"Ununoctium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Xe","A":"Neodymium","B":"Fluorine","C":"Technetium","D":"Xenon","E":"Oxygen","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Am","A":"Antimony","B":"Cadmium","C":"Aluminum","D":"Americium","E":"Actinium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cm","A":"Cesium","B":"Curium","C":"Chromium","D":"Californium","E":"Cadmium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Mo","A":"Potassium","B":"Praseodymium","C":"Molybdenum","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Neodymium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"K","A":"Potassium","B":"Nickel","C":"Hafnium","D":"Berkelium","E":"Krypton","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ar","A":"Francium","B":"Argon","C":"Americium","D":"Germanium","E":"Arsenic","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cd","A":"Chromium","B":"Carbon","C":"Cadmium","D":"Cesium","E":"Cobalt","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Tl","A":"Cobalt","B":"Tellurium","C":"Thulium","D":"Thallium","E":"Tantalum","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pa","A":"Potassium","B":"Platinum","C":"Protactinium","D":"Praseodymium","E":"Palladium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Te","A":"Tellurium","B":"Thorium","C":"Technetium","D":"Terbium","E":"Tungsten","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Uup","A":"Ununpentium","B":"Ununseptium","C":"Promethium","D":"Dysprosium","E":"Potassium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ce","A":"Cerium","B":"Chlorine","C":"Cesium","D":"Copernicium","E":"Copper","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ir","A":"Californium","B":"Iridium","C":"Iron","D":"Darmstadtium","E":"Zirconium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"La","A":"Lead","B":"Calcium","C":"Lawrencium","D":"Californium","E":"Lanthanum","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Dy","A":"Dysprosium","B":"Praseodymium","C":"Molybdenum","D":"Dubnium","E":"Neodymium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Mn","A":"Magnesium","B":"Molybdenum","C":"Manganese","D":"Meitnerium","E":"Mendelevium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Eu","A":"Erbium","B":"Praseodymium","C":"Einsteinium","D":"Europium","E":"Magnesium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Er","A":"Arsenic","B":"Erbium","C":"Seaborgium","D":"Europium","E":"Copernicium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Mt","A":"Meitnerium","B":"Mendelevium","C":"Plutonium","D":"Thallium","E":"Terbium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rh","A":"Rhodium","B":"Rutherfordium","C":"Roentgenium","D":"Rhenium","E":"Ruthenium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Fl","A":"Californium","B":"Fluorine","C":"Sulfur","D":"Flerovium","E":"Francium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Yb","A":"Beryllium","B":"Ytterbium","C":"Yttrium","D":"Dubnium","E":"Molybdenum","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ge","A":"Tungsten","B":"Gold","C":"Germanium","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Nitrogen","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ho","A":"Thorium","B":"Helium","C":"Holmium","D":"Chlorine","E":"Hydrogen","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"At","A":"Astatine","B":"Actinium","C":"Platinum","D":"Thallium","E":"Antimony","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Bk","A":"Bismuth","B":"Bohrium","C":"Barium","D":"Berkelium","E":"Bromine","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"No","A":"Neon","B":"Nitrogen","C":"Neodymium","D":"Niobium","E":"Nobelium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pt","A":"Promethium","B":"Protactinium","C":"Platinum","D":"Plutonium","E":"Potassium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Co","A":"Copper","B":"Cobalt","C":"Californium","D":"Chromium","E":"Carbon","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Na","A":"Nickel","B":"Nobelium","C":"Tantalum","D":"Uranium","E":"Sodium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Fr","A":"Francium","B":"Californium","C":"Flerovium","D":"Fermium","E":"Fluorine","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ra","A":"Americium","B":"Praseodymium","C":"Radium","D":"Radon","E":"Ruthenium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Hf","A":"Helium","B":"Rutherfordium","C":"Hafnium","D":"Hydrogen","E":"Holmium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Hs","A":"Bismuth","B":"Hassium","C":"Holmium","D":"Helium","E":"Phosphorus","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Li","A":"Livermorium","B":"Lawrencium","C":"Lutetium","D":"Lithium","E":"Polonium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Es","A":"Cesium","B":"Einsteinium","C":"Magnesium","D":"Europium","E":"Selenium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"In","A":"Iodine","B":"Iron","C":"Roentgenium","D":"Ununseptium","E":"Indium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"H","A":"Hassium","B":"Holmium","C":"Helium","D":"Hafnium","E":"Hydrogen","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Np","A":"Neptunium","B":"Neodymium","C":"Neon","D":"Ununseptium","E":"Niobium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sc","A":"Scandium","B":"Strontium","C":"Samarium","D":"Silicon","E":"Silver","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sg","A":"Seaborgium","B":"Manganese","C":"Sulfur","D":"Samarium","E":"Magnesium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Fm","A":"Francium","B":"Fluorine","C":"Californium","D":"Flerovium","E":"Fermium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Se","A":"Seaborgium","B":"Selenium","C":"Strontium","D":"Scandium","E":"Silver","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Be","A":"Bromine","B":"Ytterbium","C":"Terbium","D":"Berkelium","E":"Beryllium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Gd","A":"Gallium","B":"Gold","C":"Hydrogen","D":"Germanium","E":"Gadolinium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Md","A":"Cadmium","B":"Molybdenum","C":"Palladium","D":"Rubidium","E":"Mendelevium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ta","A":"Technetium","B":"Cobalt","C":"Thallium","D":"Tantalum","E":"Titanium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"N","A":"Neon","B":"Nobelium","C":"Nickel","D":"Niobium","E":"Nitrogen","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ne","A":"Nobelium","B":"Neptunium","C":"Nickel","D":"Neon","E":"Neodymium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Y","A":"Neodymium","B":"Yttrium","C":"Ytterbium","D":"Beryllium","E":"Dysprosium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cu","A":"Cesium","B":"Copernicium","C":"Copper","D":"Californium","E":"Cerium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Db","A":"Dysprosium","B":"Dubnium","C":"Rubidium","D":"Molybdenum","E":"Darmstadtium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Lv","A":"Lithium","B":"Lawrencium","C":"Lanthanum","D":"Livermorium","E":"Flerovium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Nb","A":"Nickel","B":"Niobium","C":"Nobelium","D":"Neptunium","E":"Bromine","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Os","A":"Silicon","B":"Osmium","C":"Dysprosium","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Potassium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rn","A":"Rhenium","B":"Roentgenium","C":"Germanium","D":"Ruthenium","E":"Radon","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"P","A":"Palladium","B":"Phosphorus","C":"Plutonium","D":"Praseodymium","E":"Protactinium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pd","A":"Protactinium","B":"Palladium","C":"Phosphorus","D":"Plutonium","E":"Praseodymium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"I","A":"Iron","B":"Indium","C":"Bohrium","D":"Iridium","E":"Iodine","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"V","A":"Silver","B":"Mendelevium","C":"Flerovium","D":"Livermorium","E":"Vanadium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"As","A":"Astatine","B":"Darmstadtium","C":"Americium","D":"Arsenic","E":"Magnesium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Zr","A":"Zinc","B":"Lawrencium","C":"Chlorine","D":"Barium","E":"Zirconium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ru","A":"Rutherfordium","B":"Rhodium","C":"Rubidium","D":"Radium","E":"Ruthenium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pb","A":"Plutonium","B":"Potassium","C":"Lead","D":"Protactinium","E":"Platinum","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"C","A":"Carbon","B":"Cerium","C":"Copper","D":"Cadmium","E":"Californium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Nd","A":"Vanadium","B":"Nickel","C":"Neodymium","D":"Nobelium","E":"Nitrogen","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rf","A":"Radium","B":"Rutherfordium","C":"Fluorine","D":"Francium","E":"Fermium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Al","A":"Lanthanum","B":"Cobalt","C":"Thallium","D":"Aluminum","E":"Argon","correct":"D"}]